Something wicked this way hops.
Wallace & Gromit: The Curse of the Were-Rabbit is a adventure,
animation, comedy film directed by Steve Box.
Cheese-loving eccentric Wallace and his cunning canine pal, Gromit, investigate a mystery in Nick Park's animated
adventure, in which the lovable inventor and his intrepid pup run a business ridding the town of garden pests.
Using only humane methods that turn their home into a halfway house for evicted vermin, the pair stumble upon a
mystery involving a voracious vegetarian monster that threatens to ruin the annual veggie-growing contest.
Wallace / Hutch (voice), played by Peter Sallis.
Victor Quartermaine (voice), played by Ralph Fiennes.
Lady Campanula Tottington (voice), played by Helena Bonham Carter.
PC Mackintosh (voice), played by Peter Kay.
Reverend Clement Hedges (voice), played by Nicholas Smith.
Mrs. Mulch (voice), played by Liz Smith.
Wallace & Gromit: The Curse of the Were-Rabbit is a platform video game
developed by Frontier Developments and published by Konami.
It was released for the PlayStation 2 and Xbox consoles.
It was released in 2005 in North America in September, Europe and Australia in October,
and in Japan the following year on 16 March 2006 for the PlayStation 2.
It is based on the film of the same name by
DreamWorks Animation and Aardman Animations.
A version for the GameCube was also announced but was never released.
The film explores themes of northern england,
hunter, competition, village, garden.
The tone is lighthearted.